Guide to the Records of the Office of the President (Oliva) RG.3.0.11
New York University Archives
- Series II. Writing and Speeches, 1963-2002; 21.2 Linear Feet in 48 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Subseries II.B Speeches, 1984-2002
    - Lucy Moses Memorial Lecture and Reception, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - George Campbell Luncheon, May 2000 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - 22nd Annual International Hospitality Industry Investment Conference Luncheon, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - William R. Salomon Reception, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - International Hospitality Industry Investment Conference Breakfast, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Administrative Management Council End of Year Reception and Dinner, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Pfizer Foundation Dedication and Master Scholars Program, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Dinner Honoring Marvin Leffler and Charlotte Frank, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - 8th Annual Protection and Transportation Services Award Ceremony, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Quebec Ministry of Research, Science and Technology Breakfast, June 2000 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Presentation of Partnership for Educational Revitalization in the Americas (PREAL) Award to President of Chile, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Lower Hudson Valley Catholic College Meeting, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - New York City Hall Lions Club Gala, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Town Hall Meeting about Commission on Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Eero Simoncelli Reception, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 2000 Alumni Association Awards Dinner, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Welcome Luncheon, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - NYU London Student Reception, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Dinner at the Savoy, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - NYU London Ribbon Cutting, Lecture, and Luncheon, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Dinner at the American Consulate, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Memorial Service for Debra James, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Tuscan American Award Ceremony, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - NYU Florence Student Reception, September 2000 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Autumn Fest Weekend, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Stern School Board of Overseers Dinner, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Foreign Policy Association Dinner, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Reception for "Marketa Kimbrell and the NYU Acting and Directing Experience", October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Varsity Club Athletics Hall of Fame Dinner, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Society of the Torch Luncheon, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Westchester Alumni Reception, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - 6th Annual Economic Development Conference, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Convocation and Luncheon Honoring Queen Sofía of Spain, October 2000 (Box 68, Folder 23, Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Loeb Reception and Portrait Unveiling, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Cocktail Reception -- Campaign for Nursing Excellence, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - School of Continuing and Professional Studies, Hospitality, Tourism, and Travel Administration Reception, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Casa Italiana 10th Anniversary, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - CAT-Ultraviolet 2000 VIP Reception, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - President's Council Reception, November 2000 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Tel Aviv University Dinner, December 2000 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Africana Studies Program and Institute of African-American Affairs Dinner, December 2000 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Recognition of Interim Dean and Presentation of Clock Dinner, December 2000 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Reception, January 2001 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Alliance Meeting -- League of World Universities, February 2001 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Bronx Borough President Fernando Ferrer, February 2001 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Preston Robert Tisch Award Dinner, February 2001 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - NYU in London Student Reception, March 2001 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 2001 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Acton Society Dinner, March 2001 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Joseph C. Park, March 2001 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Dinner, March 2001 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Northeast Conference on the Teaching of Foreign Languages Keynote Address, March 2001 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Saturday at the Square, March 2001 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Henry James Associates Meeting -- Introduction of Joan Peyser, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Washington, D. C. Alumni Reception, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Steinhardt Convocation and Dinner, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Steven T. Florio, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - President's Service Awards, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - "Teaching More Effectively with Technology" Conference, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Presidential Lecture, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Give a Violet Reception, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Kriser Family Reception, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Founders Day Convocation and Luncheon, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Student Athlete Academic Achievement Awards, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Reception, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Distinguished Administrator Awards Dinner, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Alberto Vilar Global Fellows in the Performing Arts Luncheon, April 2001 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Spain: The Best Travel Writing from 'The New York Times' Presentation, May 2001 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - ABFAS Luncheon and Award Ceremony, May 2001 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - National Scholarship Finalists Reception, May 2001 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Varsity Student Athlete Banquet, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Steinhardt School of Education Commencement, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Tisch School of Arts Commencement, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Stern Precommencement Ceremony and Nichols Award Presentation, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Commencement, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Musical Performance in the Teatrino, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Sir Harold Acton Dinner, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Musical Theater Performance, American Consulate, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Musical Theater Performance, Madrid, May 2001 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - 6th Precinct Appreciation Breakfast, June 2001 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - 9th Annual Protection and Transportation Services Awards, June 2001 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Citizen of the Village Award Dinner, June 2001 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Salute to the Washington Square Arch, September 2001 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Reception Honoring Margo Marshak, September 2001 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Reception, October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Portrait Dedication of Debra James, October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - NYU Family Gathering -- "Reaffirm Renew Restore", October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - President and Parents' Reception, October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Varsity Club Athletics Hall of Fame Dinner, October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Professorship in Law and Philanthropy Inaugural Reception and Dinner, October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Dinner Honoring Jean-Marie and Antoinette Messier, October 2001 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Association Finance Forum -- "Investing in an Era of Economic Uncertainty", November 2001 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Oscar Brand, November 2001 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Thomas G. Labrecque Smart Start Scholars Reception, November 2001 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Morning at Washington Square, November 2001 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Reception Honoring Simeon Saxe-Coburg Gotha, November 2001 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - President's Council and Cabinet Reception, November 2001 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - American Chemical Society Reception in Honor of John W. Draper, November 2001 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Reception Honoring Hugo Chávez Frías, January 2002 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Parliamentary Debate Tournament, February 2002 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Sunday at the Square, March 2002 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 25-Year Service Awards Dinner, March 2002 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Reception Honoring Jennie Grossinger, March 2002 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Conversations at Washington Square with Zoë Caldwell, March 2002 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Saturday at the Square, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Silver Professorships Reception and Dinner, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Washington, D. C. Alumni Reception, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Presidential Lecture with Bruce Bueno de Mesquita, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - St. Thomas Aquinas College Honors Convocation, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Preston Robert Tisch Award Dinner, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Kriser Family Reception, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - 6th Annual Alumni Association Awards Dinner, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Founders Day, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Student Athlete Academic Achievement Awards, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Distinguished Administrator Awards Dinner, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholars Reception, April 2002 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - 10th Reunion Celebration, April 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Give a Violet Reception, April 2002 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - National Scholarship Finalists Reception, May 2002 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - ABFAS Luncheon and Award Ceremony, May 2002 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Reception Honoring Nelson Mandela, May 2002 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Reception Honoring Peter King, May 2002 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, May 2002 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Villa La Pietra Events, May 2002 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - "Universities in the 21st Century", undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Series III. Administrative Files, 1979-2002; 3.02 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 5 oversized flat boxes
  This series consists of day-to-day materials, such as calendars, phone lists, and reports on facilities and construction projects. It also includes biographical material on Oliva, such as curriculum vitae, personal slides from a trip abroad, and awards and honors. Materials also include information on the history of NYU and statistics related to awards and fellowships received by NYU students, alumni, and faculty.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic except for the first folder.
  - Biographical File, 1979-1996 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Honors, 1987-2002 (Box 74, Folder 2, Box 130, Folder 6, Box 132, Folder 2-3, Box 133, Folder 3-4, Box 135, Folder 5, Box 141)
  - Calendars, 1990-2001 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Facilities, 1987-2000 (Box 74, Folder 4, Box 135, Folder 3)
  - NYU History and Statistics, 1987-2000 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Phone Lists, 1992-1995 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Series IV. Associations, 1987-2002; 3.06 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes
  This series contains files collected by Oliva on organizations with which he regularly interacted or served in some capacity, either as an honorary member, committee member, or board member. The files typically contain organization reports, publications, correspondence, and meeting notes. These files reflect his commitments to higher education, as seen in his participation with the Institute of International Education; athletics, as noted in his participation with the University Athletic Association; and global education, as seen with the Council on Foreign Relations.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Lists of Board and Committee Memberships, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education, 1991-1995 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - The American Museum of Immigration, 1991-1993 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Association for a Better New York (ABNY), 1991-1994 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU), 1992-1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Associazione Liguri Nel Mondo, 1992-1996 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Business-Higher Education Forum, 1992-1994 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Chatham House, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - CICU, 1992-2000 (Box 75, Folder 9-10)
  - The Conference Board, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Consortium of Social Science Associations, 1992-1999 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - The Council for the United States and Italy, 1998-1999 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Council of Advisors on Education, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1991-1999 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Fighting Back, 1991-1994 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Friends of LaGuardia Place, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Institute of International Education, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Institute of International Education, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Institute of International Education, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 10, Box 77, Folder 1-2)
  - Institute of International Education, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
  - Institute of International Education, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
  - Institute of International Education, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - The Ireland-United States Council for Commerce and Industry, 1994-2001 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - The Irish American Cultural Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - John Henry Newman Foundation, University College Dublin, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1989-1991 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - League of World Universities, 1998-2001 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Metro International, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Meucci Memorial Committee, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - National Academy Foundation, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities (NAICU), 1992-1999 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) Presidents Commission, 1993-1995 (Box 78, Folder 11-12)
  - New York City Academy of Public Service, 1992-1994 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - New York City Partnership, 1992-1998 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - New York State Commission on National and Community Service, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - New York State Compact for Learning, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Nonprofit CEO Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - NYC2012, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - NYUonline, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - The Phi Beta Kappa Society, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - The Rhodes Scholarship Trust, 1999-2001 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Russian-American Press and Information Center, 1992-1996 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Songwriters' Hall of Fame, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - United Nations Association of New York, 1992-1994 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - University Athletic Association (UAA), 1991-2001 (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
  - Washington Square Music Festival, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - The White House Conference on a Drug Free America, 1987-1988 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Series V. Development and Finance, 1990-2002; 1.75 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access to this series is restricted.
  This series includes development files (donor briefings, fundraising reports, and grant applications), and budgets, reports, and audits provided to the President's office from university departments, divisions, and organizations.
  Arranged chronologically by topic (Donor Briefings, Budgets, etc.).
  - Donor Briefings, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Donor Briefings, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 2-4)
  - Donor Briefings, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 5-6)
  - Donor Briefings, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 7-8)
  - Donor Briefings, 1994-2002 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1990-1992 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, 1994-1999 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising, 1990-1995 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising, 1997-2002 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Senior Vice President for Finance, 1991-1993 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Deputy Vice President for Budget and Planning, 1991-2001 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Vice President for Finance, 1994-2001 (Box 83, Folder 3-5)
  - Vice President for External Affairs, 1995-2002 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
  - Vice President for Institutional Advancement, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Committee on Financial Aid, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Development Committee, 1994-2001 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - NYU Community Fund Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Senate Financial Affairs Committee, 1991-1996 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Series VI. Events and Programs, 1987-2002; 4.83 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 1 flat oversized box
  This series contains invitations, programs, correspondence, and agendas for various events, including commencements, receptions, dinners, conferences, and award ceremonies, attended by Oliva as part of his presidential duties. Oliva delivered speeches and addresses for many of these events, which are located in Series II. There is a small amount of material from Oliva's previous positions.
  - Events -- General, 1987-February 1991 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Event Photographs, circa 1989-1996 (Box 85, Folder 2, Box 135, Folder 1)
  - NYU Presidential Inauguration, November 1991 (Box 85, Folder 3-6, Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - Events -- General, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Events -- General, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 4-5)
  - Women of Color in Higher Education Conference, March 1993 (Box 87, Folder 1-3)
  - Humanities Luncheon, July 1993 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Social Sciences Luncheon, July 1993 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Events -- General, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Villa La Pietra Meeting, January 1994 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Events, General, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - International Rectors' Conference, February 1995 (Box 88, Folder 5-6, Box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Academic Convocation in Honor of Kim Young Sam, October 1995 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Events -- General, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 4-5)
  - International Rectors' Conference, January 1996 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
  - International Rectors' Technical Conference, April 1996 (Box 90, Folder 3-4)
  - Commencement, May 1996 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Villa La Pietra Trip, September 1996 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Events -- General, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 7, Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Events -- General, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 2-3)
  - Events -- General, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Villa La Pietra Events, December 1999 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Events -- General, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Events -- General, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Events -- General, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 2-3)
  - Events -- General, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Series VII. Governance, 1986-2002; 9.63 Linear Feet in 22 manuscript boxes
  Access to this series is restricted until 2037.
  This series consists of materials created by the different governing bodies at NYU. As president of the university, Oliva was a member of most of these governing bodies. The majority of the files consist of Board of Trustees materials, such as agendas, meeting minutes, memos, and member files; additionally, there are board materials for individual schools (such as the Medical School and School of Law), committee files, and University Senate files, all of which include agendas, meeting meetings, and memos. The University Senate files also contain the annual "State of the University" addresses.
  - Administrative Management Council, 1991-1994 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Africana Studies Committee, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - All-University Selection Committee, 1996-2000 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association/Council Board of Directors, 1990-1998 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Association of Black Faculty, Administrators, and Staff, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Board of Regents, State Education Department, 1989-2002 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Lists, 1989-1999 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Newsletters, 1989-1990 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, April-June 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, September-November 1991 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, December 1991 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, January-February 1992 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, March-May 1992 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, October-December 1992 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, March 1993 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, May 1993 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, September-December 1993 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, March-June 1994 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, September-December 1994 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, February-May 1995 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, July-September 1995 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, October-December 1995 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, February-June 1997 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, September-December 1997 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, March-April 1998 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, May-September 1998 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, October-November 1998 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, December 1998 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, January-March 1999 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, April-May 1999 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, September-December 1999 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, February-August 2000 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, September-December 2000 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Leadership Retreat, February 2001 (Box 98, Folder 5, Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, March-December 2001 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Agendas and Meetings, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Academic Affairs Committee, 1991-1995 (Box 99, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Audit Committee, 1991-1996 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Audit Committee, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Audit Committee, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 2-4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Compensation Committee, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 5-6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Compensation Committee, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Development Committee, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Committee, 1991-1998 (Box 101, Folder 5-6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1994-2001 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Y2K Committee, 1999 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Board of Visitors -- Institute of French Studies, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Casa Italiana Advisory Committee, 1996-2001 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - City of New York, 1999-2001 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - College of Dentistry Dean's Advisory Board, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Commission on an Internationalized Community, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Communications Advisory Board, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 8)